You're cordially invited to a violently romantic comedy.
Borderline is a comedy, horror, thriller film directed by Jimmy Warden.
After escaping from a mental hospital, a violent sociopath named Paul begins a
dangerous rampage targeting Sofia, a world-famous pop star.
Obsessed with her, he takes Sofia hostage in her own home, acting under
the delusional belief that they are getting married.
Paul is desperate to prove his devotion, leading to a
tense and unpredictable situation.
Sofia Minor, played by Samara Weaving.
Paul Duerson, played by Ray Nicholson.
DeVante Rhodes, played by Jimmie Fails.
Bell, played by Eric Dane.
Penny, played by Alba Baptista.
Eleanor, played by Catherine Lough Haggquist.
Borderline is a 2025 American comedy thriller film written and
directed by Jimmy Warden in his directorial debut.
Starring Samara Weaving, Ray Nicholson, Jimmie Fails, Alba Baptista, and Eric Dane, the film centers on a pop star (Weaving) whose home is invaded
by an obsessive fan (Nicholson) who believes they are meant to get married and manipulates her into going along with his delusion.
The film was released in the United States on March 14, 2025, by Magnet
Releasing, and received mixed to positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of pop star, obsession,
bodyguard, dark comedy, hallucination.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.